export const stateQuestionArray = {
    questions: [
        {
            question:
                "Utah",
            choices: ["Tooele", "Salt Lake City",    "Provo", "St. George"],
            type: "MCQ's",
            correctAnswer: "Salt Lake City",
        },

        {
            question:
                "Colorado",
            choices: [ "Boulder", "Colorado Springs", "Salt Lake City",   "Denver"],
            type: "MCQ's",
            correctAnswer: "Denver",
        },

        {
            question:
                "Arizona",
            choices: ["Phoenix", "Mesa", "Tucson", "Flagstaff"],
            type: "MCQ's",
            correctAnswer: "Phoenix",
        },

        {
            question:
                "California",
            choices: ["San Diego", "Los Angeles", "Sacramento", "San Francisco"],
            type: "MCQ's",
            correctAnswer: "Sacramento",
        },

        {
            question:
                "Oregon",
            choices: ["Salem", "San Francisco", "Portland", "Eugene"],
            type: "MCQ's",
            correctAnswer: "Salem",
        },

        {
            question:
                "Washington",
            choices: ["Seattle", "Tacoma", "Spokane", "Olympia"],
            type: "MCQ's",
            correctAnswer: "Olympia",
        },

        {
            question:
                "Idaho",
            choices: ["Twin Falls", "Boise", "Idaho Falls", "Coeur d'Alene"],
            type: "MCQ's",
            correctAnswer: "Boise",
        },

        {
            question:
                "Nevada",
            choices: ["Las Vegas", "Reno", "Carson City", "Elko"],
            type: "MCQ's",
            correctAnswer: "Carson City",
        },

        {
            question:
                "Montana",
            choices: ["Helena", "Butte", "Missoula", "Billings"],
            type: "MCQ's",
            correctAnswer: "Helena",
        },

        {
            question:
                "New Mexico",
            choices: ["Albuquerque", "Las Cruces", "Roswell", "Santa Fe"],
            type: "MCQ's",
            correctAnswer: "Santa Fe",
        },

        {
            question:
                "Wyoming",
            choices: ["Sheridan", "Gillette", "Rock Springs", "Cheyenne"],
            type: "MCQ's",
            correctAnswer: "Cheyenne",
        },

        {
            question:
                "North Dakota",
            choices: ["Fargo", "Bismark", "Jamestown", "Medora"],
            type: "MCQ's",
            correctAnswer: "Boise",
        },

        {
            question:
                "South Dakota",
            choices: ["Sioux Falls", "Pierre", "Sturgis", "Rapid City"],
            type: "MCQ's",
            correctAnswer: "Pierre",
        },

        {
            question:
                "Nebraska",
            choices: ["North Platte", "Lincoln", "Omaha", "Grand Island"],
            type: "MCQ's",
            correctAnswer: "Lincoln",
        },

        {
            question:
                "Kansas",
            choices: ["Topeka", "Dodge City", "Kansas City", "Witchita"],
            type: "MCQ's",
            correctAnswer: "Topeka",
        },

        {
            question:
                "Oklahoma",
            choices: ["Tulsa", "Elk City", "Oklahoma City", "Plano"],
            type: "MCQ's",
            correctAnswer: "Oklahoma City",
        },

        {
            question:
                "Texas",
            choices: ["Austin", "Houston", "Dallas", "Galveston"],
            type: "MCQ's",
            correctAnswer: "Austin",
        },

        {
            question:
                "Louisiana",
            choices: ["Shreveport", "New Orleans", "Lafayette", "Baton Rouge"],
            type: "MCQ's",
            correctAnswer: "Baton Rouge",
        },

        {
            question:
                "Arkansas",
            choices: ["Little Rock", "Bentonville", "Fayetteville", "Conway"],
            type: "MCQ's",
            correctAnswer: "Little Rock",
        },

        {
            question:
                "Missouri",
            choices: ["Branson", "Jefferson City", "St. Louis", "Springfield"],
            type: "MCQ's",
            correctAnswer: "Jefferson City",
        },

        {
            question:
                "Iowa",
            choices: ["Des Moines", "Dubuque", "Cedar Rapids", "Iowa City"],
            type: "MCQ's",
            correctAnswer: "Des Moines",
        },

        {
            question:
                "Minnesota",
            choices: ["Rochester", "Minneaplolis", "Cedar Rapids", "St. Cloud"],
            type: "MCQ's",
            correctAnswer: "St. Paul",
        },

    ]
};

export const resultInitialState = {
    score: 0,
    correctAnswers: 0,
    wrongAnswers: 0,
};